[{"question": "Choose a right C Statement.", "option1": "A) Loops or Repetition block executes a group of statements repeatedly.", "option2": "B) Loop is usually executed as long as a condition is met.", "option3": "C) Loops usually take advantage of Loop Counter", "option4": "D) All the above.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Loops in C Language are implemented using.?", "option1": "A) While Block", "option2": "B) For Block", "option3": "C) Do While Block", "option4": "D) All the above", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Which loop is faster in C Language, for, while or Do While.?", "option1": "A) for", "option2": "B) while", "option3": "C) do while", "option4": "D) All work at same speed", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "Choose correct C while loop syntax.", "option1": "A) while(condition)\n{\n    //statements\n}\n", "option2": "B) {\n    //statements\n}while(condition)\n", "option3": "C) while(condition);\n{\n    //statements\n}\n", "option4": "D) while()\n{\n    if(condition)\n    {\n        //statements\n    }\n}\n", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "Choose a correct C for loop syntax.", "option1": "A) for(initalization; condition; incrementoperation)\n{\n    //statements\n}\n", "option2": "B) for(declaration; condition; incrementoperation)\n{\n    //statements\n}\n", "option3": "C) for(declaration; incrementoperation; condition)\n{\n    //statements\n}\n", "option4": "D) for(initalization; condition; incrementoperation;)\n{\n    //statements\n}\n", "ans": "A"}, {"question": "Choose a correct C do while syntax.", "option1": "A) dowhile(condition)\n{\n    //statements\n}\n", "option2": "B) do while(condition)\n{\n    //statements\n}\n", "option3": "C) do\n{\n    //statements\n\n}while(condition)\n", "option4": "D) do\n{\n    //statements\n\n}while(condition);\n", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    while(true)    \n    {\n        printf(\"RABBIT\");\n        break;\n    }\n    \n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) RABBIT", "option2": "B) RABBIT is printed unlimited number of times.", "option3": "C) No output", "option4": "D) Compiler error.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=5;\n    \n    while(a==5)    \n    {\n        printf(\"RABBIT\");\n        break;\n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) RABBIT is printed unlimited number of times", "option2": "B) RABBIT", "option3": "C) Compiler error", "option4": "D) None of the above.", "ans": "B"}, {"question": "What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=5;\n    \n    while(a=123)    \n    {\n        printf(\"RABBIT\\n\");\n        break;\n    }\n    printf(\"GREEN\");\n    \n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) GREEN", "option2": "B) RABBIT\nGREEN", "option3": "C) RABBIT is printed\u00a0unlimited number of times.", "option4": "D) Compiler error.", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=5;\n    \n    while(a >= 3);\n    {\n        printf(\"RABBIT\\n\");\n        break;\n    }\n    printf(\"GREEN\");\n    \n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) GREEN", "option2": "B) RABBIT\nGREEN", "option3": "C) RABBIT is printed infinite times", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=25;\n    \n    while(a <= 27)\n    {\n        printf(\"%d \", a);\n        a++;\n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 25 25 25", "option2": "B) 25 26 27", "option3": "C) 27 27 27", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=32;\n    \n    do\n    {\n        printf(\"%d \", a);\n        a++;\n    }while(a <= 30);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 32", "option2": "B) 33", "option3": "C) 30", "option4": "D) No Output", "ans": "A"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int a=32;\n    \n    do\n    {\n        printf(\"%d \", a);\n        a++;\n        if(a > 35)\n            break;\n    }while(1);\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) No Output", "option2": "B) 32 33 34", "option3": "C) 32 33 34 35", "option4": "D) Compiler error", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " Choose a correct C Statement.", "option1": "A) a++ is (a=a+1) POST INCREMENT Operator", "option2": "B) a-- is (a=a-1) POST DECREMENT Opeartor\n--a is (a=a-1) PRE DECREMENT Opeator", "option3": "C) ++a is (a=a+1) PRE INCRMENT Operator", "option4": "D) All the above.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " Choose correct Syntax for C Arithmetic Compound Assignment Operators.", "option1": "A) a+=b\u00a0is (a= a+ b)\na-=b is (a= a-b)", "option2": "B) a*=b is (a=a*b)\na/=b is (a = a/b)", "option3": "C) a%=b is (a=a%b)", "option4": "D) All the above.", "ans": "D"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int k, j;\n    \n    for(k=1, j=10; k <= 5; k++)\n    {\n        printf(\"%d \", (k+j));\n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) compiler error", "option2": "B) 10 10 10 10 10", "option3": "C) 11 12 13 14 15", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int k;\n    \n    for(k=1; k <= 5; k++);\n    {\n        printf(\"%d \", k);\n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) 1 2 3 4 5", "option2": "B) 1 2 3 4", "option3": "C) 6", "option4": "D) 5", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int k;\n    \n    for(;;)\n    {\n        printf(\"TESTING\\n\");\n        break;\n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) No Output", "option2": "B) TESTING", "option3": "C) Compiler error", "option4": "D) None of the above", "ans": "B"}, {"question": " What is the output of C Program.?\nint main()\n{\n    int k;\n    \n    for(printf(\"FLOWER \"); printf(\"YELLOW \"); printf(\"FRUITS \"))\n    {\n        break;\n    }\n\n    return 0;\n}\n", "option1": "A) Compiler error", "option2": "B) FLOWER FRUITS", "option3": "C) FLOWER YELLOW", "option4": "D) FLOWER YELLOW FRUITS", "ans": "C"}, {"question": " What is the way to suddenly come out of or Quit any Loop in C Language.?", "option1": "A) continue; statement", "option2": "B) break; statement", "option3": "C) leave; statement", "option4": "D) quit; statement", "ans": "B"}]
